<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mohneesh Sreegirisetty</title>
    <link>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mohneesh Sreegirisetty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Detection and Trip Count using OpenCV and YoLoV3</title>
      <link>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/posts/opencv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/posts/opencv/</guid>
      <description>Background on the Task     Object Detection is the process of identifying things from an image or a video. It can be used tin many practical applications such as security, face detection, vehicle detection etc. We try to detect objects in the given video.
 In this day and age CCTV video monitoring has become a tedious task and is very time taking and very error-prone. This project of ours will take on that problem as we try to solve the ever existing problem of CCTV monitoring, mainly vehicle and human detection and frequency assertion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handwritten Character Recognition With Own Dataset</title>
      <link>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/posts/handwritten-character-recognnition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/posts/handwritten-character-recognnition/</guid>
      <description>Introduction    We train the machine to recognize handwritten Alphabets. We prepared our own dataset for the project. This trained machine learning model can be then used in various other applications like word recognition, English OCR etc. All the relevant code can be found Here.This was the first Mini-Project that I did in my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s. This project was done under the guidance of Mr. Amit Patel.
The Data for the Task    This data has been collected and segmented manually by my team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>  Loading…  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>🙋🏽‍♂️ My name is Mohneesh Sreegirisetty. I completed my B.Tech from IIIT Nuzvid in 2019. I am very interested in Machine Learning / Artificial Intelligence . Programs that can think for themselves and take decisions based on its knowledge (or without the knowledge) is very fascinating indeed. Hence I aspire to be a data scientist.I have an in-depth knowledge of how various machine learning algorithms work and am pretty confident in my coding skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects 📒</title>
      <link>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohneesh7.github.io/my-portfolio/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my projects with thier Github Links, To know more about each of them check out the Blog section.    Handwritten Character Recognition using Own Dataset    Using SVM and other techniques to create a model which would predict/recognize the english alphabet from our own dataset.
For more Information on this refer my blog : Here
Vehicle Detection and Trip Count Using OpenCV and YOLO    This is my final year project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
